https://cvm.org/privacy-policy/

AboutOur StoryOur TeamFinancial IntegrityFAQBlogContact
Missions
Short-Term MissionsHow it WorksCurrent OpportunitiesApplicationPay FeesShort-Term Missions Forms
Long-Term MissionsWhy CVM?How it WorksCurrent OpportunitiesApplyLong-Term Mission Forms
Mission ApprenticeshipMission Apprenticeship FormsField Staff
Get InvolvedReal Life Real ImpactRegion Representative
ProfessionalsBecome an AmbassadorFind Your CVF GroupGlobal AffiliatesFor Your Practice
StudentsFind Your CVF GroupExternshipsWays To GiveVolunteerEvents
ResourceseLearningJob BoardFor ProfessionalsFor StudentsBooksForms
Use of Links
Throughout our Web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers.
Creating a text link from your Web site to our site does not require permission. If you have a link you’d like us to consider adding to our Web site, please send email to info@cvm.orgwith the subject “Link request.”
Use of Text and Images
If you would like to publish information that you find on our Web site, please send your request to info@cvm.org. Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page.
Accessibility
This Web site is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities, and to comply with federal guidelines concerning accessibility. We welcome your comments. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible, please contact us at info@cvm.org.
Online Donations
If you complete the donation form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary.
You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the “Opt Out” section below.
Web Site Privacy Policy
We have created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site.
Reading or Downloading
We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or princeton.edu if you are connecting from Princeton University’s domain), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site.We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.
Online Profile Updates and Donations
If you complete the Profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary.
You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the “Opt Out” section below.
Sending us an Email
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer your questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.
We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.
If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We won’t share your name or email address with any outside parties.
Kids and Privacy
For children who visit our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city. When kids send email to us, their online contact information (email address) is not used to re-contact them and is not maintained in retrievable form.
Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from through a special online form. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us through another online form. You can not remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication.
Security
We are committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use Internet encryption software, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol, when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card, login and password information.
Cookies
We use “cookies” to track your preferences and activities on the cvm.org website or any other Christian Veterinary Mission related sites. Cookies are small data files transferred to your computer’s hard-drive by a website. They keep a record of your preferences making your subsequent visits to the site more efficient.
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit www.allaboutcookies.org. “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.“Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Questions about our policies:
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at info@cvm.org.
Sign up to receive our Newsletter
